const Data = [{
    question:'What does HTML stand for?',
options :['Hyper Text Markup Language',
          'Hot Mail'  ,
          'How to Make Lasagna', 
],
      correctAns: "Hyper Text Markup Language"
},{

  question:'What is the difference between an opening tag and a closing tag?',
  options :['Opening tag has a / in front',
            'Closing tag has a / in front'  ,
            'There is no difference', 
  ],
        correctAns: "Opening tag has a / in front"
  },
{

  question:'< br  / > What type of tag is this?',
  options :['Break tag',
            'A broken one'  ,
            'An opening tag', 
  ],
        correctAns: "Break tag"
  },
{

  question:'< body > Is this an opening tag or a closing tag?',
  options :['Opening',
            'Closing'  , 
  ],
        correctAns: "Opening"
  },
{

  question:'Where is the meta tag only found?',
  options :['The last page',
            'The home page'  , 
            'The second page'  , 
  ],
        correctAns: "The home page"
  },

  {question:'What is an element that does not have a closing tag called?',
  options :['Tag',
            'Empty element'  , 
            'Closed element'  , 
  ],
        correctAns: "Empty element"
  },

  {question:'Which of the following is an example of an empty element?',
  options :[' < img / >',
            ' < img > < / img >'  , 
            '< / img>'  , 
  ],
        correctAns: "< img > < / img >"
  },
  {question:'What should values always be enclosed in?',
  options :['  Quotation marks',
            ' Commas'  , 
            'Parenthesis'  , 
  ],
        correctAns: "Parenthesis"
  },
  {question:'Where do all items for the same website need to be saved?',
  options :['In the same folder',
            'Where ever is fine'  , 
            'In different folders'  , 
  ],
        correctAns: "In the same folder"
  },
  {question:'What does < a  h r e f = ”h t t p : / / w w w . g o o g l e . c o m“  t i t l e = ” L i n k  t o   G o o g l e  ” t a r g e t = ” _  b l a n k  ” > G o o g l e  < / a > do?',
  options :[' Adds a link to google on the page',
            ' Adds a search engine to the page'  , 
            'Nothing'  , 
  ],
        correctAns: "Adds a link to google on the page"
  },
]

export default Data;


